(Sheldon:)September 22nd.
(Sheldon:)Right,
the weekend after Leonard's dog died.
(Leonard:)Mitzy's dead?
(Sheldon:)She was old and blind, Leonard.
What choice did we have?
(Leonard:)I don't believe this.
Why am I the last to know?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
I am the one getting a divorce...
(Beverley:)...Mitzy is the one who is dead,
why are you the one making a fuss?
You're right. I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)I'm way out of line.
(Beverley:)Penny, what's new in your life?
(Penny:)Nothing. Not a damn thing.
(Beverley:)Thank you for driving me
back to my hotel.
(Penny:)Oh, it's not a problem.
(Beverley:)I was going to ask Leonard to do it, but
he seemed a bit emotionally unstable...
(Beverley:)...and you don't want someone like that
operating heavy machinery.
(Penny:)No, you do not.
Your "check engine" light is on.
(Penny:)Yeah, I gotta put a sticker over that.